<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Alessandro Pellizzari</title><link>https://alessandro23pellizzari.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Alessandro Pellizzari</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://alessandro23pellizzari.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://alessandro23pellizzari.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alessandro23pellizzari.github.io/about/</guid><description>Professional Profile Link to heading I am a highly competent developer and IT professional with experience in web development, backend development, mobile development, database management and application integrations. I have strong technical skills as well as good interpersonal skills, enabling me to fit in any team and work both on the technical and functional tasks. I am a highly competitive person, always ready to learn and expand my knowledge to grow and further improve my skills.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://alessandro23pellizzari.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alessandro23pellizzari.github.io/contact/</guid><description> Contact me Link to heading Name Email address Message Submit</description></item><item><title/><link>https://alessandro23pellizzari.github.io/it/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alessandro23pellizzari.github.io/it/about/</guid><description>Professional Profile Link to heading I am a highly competent IT professional with track record in mobile development, full stack web development and database management. I have strong technical skills as well as good interpersonal skills, enabling me to fit and work together in a team to reach goals and resolving problems and challenges that may arise. I am an highly competitive person, always ready learn and expand my knowledge in order to grow and further improve my skills.</description></item></channel></rss>